
[About]

Thank you for your continued support of Project HiNAtyu.

This GSC mod is supported for the following game titles:

Call of Duty Modern Warfare (2019) / MW19 / MW2019 / IW8 / CoD16
Additionally, it supports the following versions of MW2019:

Donetsk 1.20 (Dev build)
Retail Version (with MRON AIO GSC Injector)
This repository contains the source code of the Quick Scope Lobby GSC, which was released for learning purposes, as well as the compiled GSCBIN for actual play.

----------

[YouTube Video]

For installation guidance, please check the video below:
https://youtu.be/37-kYwvO0Q0

If pressing the "Load script" button in MRON AIO GSC Injector results in no response, please refer to the following fix video:
https://youtu.be/AFinja6Ephs

----------

[Description of the GSC Mod]

By installing this GSC Mod, you can apply the custom game mode "Quick Scope Lobby" to your lobby.

After starting the match, select your loadout and ensure that text is displayed on the bottom-left corner of the screen after spawning.

You can enable or disable the features through the following actions.

----------

Function : Enable / Disable Quick Scope Lobby
Bind : Ads + Use
ex. Right click + F key (KBM)
ex. L2 Trigger + Square Button (PS Controller)

Function : Change language (EN, JA, CN, RU, DE)
Bind : Ads + Melee
ex. Right click + V key (KBM)
ex. L2 Trigger + R Stick Button (PS Controller)

----------

When Quick Scope Lobby is enabled, all players in the lobby will have their weapons forcibly stripped.
Afterwards, a handgun for trick shots and a sniper rifle will be randomly assigned to each player.

Weapons are randomly selected from a variety of camos, attachments, and blueprints.
Depending on the random selection, you may even end up fighting with a rare sniper rifle.

If you engage in camping behavior during gameplay, the GSC system will detect it.
After a warning appears on the screen, you will be launched into the air as a penalty, three seconds after the camping behavior is detected.

Additionally, if you perform a long scope for more than one second during gameplay, the GSC system will detect the long-scope action.
A warning message will appear on the screen, and then the aim will be released immediately.

These features ensure that you can enjoy a fair sniper battle with your friends.

This custom game mode can be executed on any map and in any game mode.
Additionally, this lobby is enforced for friends who join midway, ensuring fairness in all aspects.

Please enjoy!